travour.com 2018-06-29

# Real Time Flight Information Status

We at Travour.com a subsidiary of Compare Infobase Ltd are committed to safeguarding your online privacy. Please do read the following policy to understand how your private information will be treated while you make full use of our e-shopping or other offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please come back to check periodically. Compare Infobase Pvt. Ltd or its subsidiary Travour.com may collect the information explained herein under. 

1.We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, contact us dsahoo@itrix.biz

2.What identifiable information is collected from me? 

Travour.com may collect information in one or more ways from different parts of our network of Web sites. 

Travour.com may ask you for personal information at times, including, but not limited to, when you enter in a contest or promotion sponsored by Travour.com and/or our other contracted partners; and when you report a problem with one of our sites or services. Travour.com occasionally may also ask site user to complete surveys that are use for internal research. Wherever Travour.com collects personal information an effort is made to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

3\. What are cookies and how Travour.com uses them?

As combined part of offering and providing customised and personalised services, Travour.com may use cookies to store and track your information. A cookie is a miniscule amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server that may be stored on your computer's hard drive. If you choose to have Compare Infobase Pvt. Ltd. browse map images, routes and trip plans we will require that you accept cookies. 

Cache your personalised settings for items such as route language and default country location.Determine whether you are using a public computer so that any Travour.com settings changed while using a public computer do not affect the next user's ability to use Travour.com 

Roughly Estimate our audience or browsers. Each fresh browser trying to access Travour.com may be given a cookie. That maybe used to determine the extent of repeat usage by the user. 

Assist us to track the number of visits to and business activities at the Travour.com or Travour.com store, and to track and process the items in your shopping basket. 

Track your progress and number of entries or queries in some of our promotions, and contests. When a Compare Infobase-hosted promotion uses cookies, the information written to the cookie may be used to track the entries, submissions made, and status in prize drawings list. 

Measure certain specific traffic patterns to the site, track the areas of Travour.com network of Web sites visited, track the Web site or geographical location through which you came to Travour.com and your visiting patterns in average. We use this research to understand our users' visit habits and browsing preferences of if they are similar or different from one another so that we can make each visit by you on Travour.com better experience then last one. We may use this information to better the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will be likely to see on our sites. 

Travour.com also collects geophysical IP addresses for system and server administration and to report visiting information to our advertisers.

Other advertising networks that may serve advertisings onto Travour.com network may also use their own cookies. 

Travour.com and its advertisers may also use small pieces of code called ''web beacons'' or electronic images that are sometime called "single-pixel GIF" to collect anonymous and average advertising patterns, such as counting hits, browser type, time spent viewing a page, type of page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our anonymous cookie policy. Travour.com does not allow access or sell other advertisers or their advertising networks, information collected from you. 

4\. Who is collecting information?

When you are visiting a Travour.com site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information for use by Travour.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Some Travour.com services may be offered in conjunction with a third partner. In order to provide this service to you, it may be necessary for us to share your personal information with our partner company. In such cases you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. Where as if you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of such data by not using that particular service at all. 

Sometime promotions that run on Travour.com network sites may be sponsored by companies other than Travour.com or may be co-sponsored by Travour.com and another company. Some or all data collected during such a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. In the event of data being shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. So you can decide whether to participate in the promotion, if you don't want your data to be shared. 

Please be advised that Travour.com advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. Such information practices of those Web sites linked to Travour.com are expressly not covered by this privacy statement. 

5\. With who else Travour.com will share my information? 

As a thumb rule, Travour.com will not wilfully disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under extraneous circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Described herein under are some of the ways that your information may be shared or disclosed. 

Sponsors & Business Partners: : Travour.com may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is specifically and expressly described to you at the time of data collection or prior to transferring the data. Some or all data collected during a Travour.com promotion may be shared with a sponsor. If a part of personally identifying data about you will be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data. 

During many promotions offers you may be requested for additional information from sponsors. By requesting more information, you give Travour.com permission to transfer your personal information to the sponsor so they can fulfil your request. In majority of instances, only your email address will be shared. 

Third Party Data & Data Comparisons: Under confidentiality agreements, Travour.com may match user information with third party data. Also, Travour.com discloses patterned user statistics in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and or other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

Miscellaneous: Travour.com may also disclose user information in such cases where we have reason to believe that disclosure of this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Compare Infobase Pvt. Ltd's rights or property, other Travour.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Travour.com may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law or law-enforcing agency requires it. 

6\. Do I have choices or controls regarding collection, use, and distribution of my identifiable information?

Upon your express interest about receiving offers or information from Travour.com and our partners under confidentiality, may occasionally send you e-mail or postal mail about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you and only if you indicated that you welcome these offers. Any time you can easily unsubscribe from Compare Infobase Pvt. Ltd's mailing list and no longer receive such offers and mailings. 

On some types of Travour.com promotions, we will ask for your email address in order to update you on your score, entries, and status in prize drawings. Your participation in these types of promotions, may automatically enlist you to receive promotion-related email. Sometime these promotion-related emails may include targeted advertisements. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use some of Travour.com services that require the use of cookies in order to participate. 

Travour.com as a policy does not sell or rent your information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. You can choose not to use a particular service or not to participate in certain promotions or contests, if you do not wish to allow such data sharing. 

7\. How much protected is my personal financial information?

To keep your personal financial information private is vital and important to us. As with all personal information, Travour.com will never rent or sell your personal financial information. Your use of certain services or features, known to us, may help us to offer you better and more relevant content and advertisements. Yet as with all personally identifiable information, we do not make this available to any third parties without your permission. 

Please note that there may be places on the Travour.com network of Web sites where you can transmit credit card information in order to complete a purchase transaction or for verification purposes. Any time we ask for a credit card number we transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use best industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption technology. This sophisticated encryption process ensures that prying eyes are unable to decode your personal data when it travels from your computer to ours. 

8\. What security precautions are there to place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information? 

It may not be a norm but the fact remains that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure always. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Travour.com cannot ensure or warrant the total security of any information you transmit to us or for our online products purchase or services, and you do so at your own risk. But once we receive your transmission, we strive and make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

9\. What else should I know about my privacy?

Do keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, on mailing lists or in chat areas - that information can be seen and collected and used by others. In nutshell, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the other public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Finally, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any registration information. Please be careful and responsible on your own whenever you're online. 

10\. Is there any children's privacy? 

Yes, the safety of children is very important to us. Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to Compare Infobase Pvt. Ltd, or to anyone online for that matter. Travour.com does not share personal information about users under the age of 13 with third parties under any circumstances unless there is a special situation and such information is requested by law enforcing agency and we do not sell or rent personal information about any of our users, regardless of their age. In addition, Travour.com will not send any direct email offers to users who indicate they are under the age of 14 without first obtaining their parents' permission.

11\. Advertising cookies 

This site has contracted with Travel Ad Network and its third party ad-serving technology provider Atlas, a Microsoft Corporation Subsidiary, to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs',advertisement impressions,and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, Travel Ad Network may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors.No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by Travel Ad Network,please see Travel Ad Network?s privacy policy at http://www.traveladnetwork.com/content/view/56/79/.
